cu-athome.org 2006-12-30

# Sandia Laboratory Federal Credit Union

|  |  |  |  |   
---  
|  _No Response Required.  
Please [feel free to contact us with any questions. ](mailto:ebranch@slfcu.org)_

Sandia Laboratory Federal Credit Union is owned by its members and governed by a Board of Directors you elect. We do everything we can to protect the privacy of members, joint account owners, beneficiaries, and consumers, including those who visit our Web site. We are required by law to give you this privacy notice to explain how we collect, use and safeguard your non-public personal information.  

We know how important safeguarding personal information is to our members, and we share your concerns. **You have entrusted us with meeting your financial needs, and we recognize that a critical part of our job in meeting your needs is respecting and preserving your privacy.  

** **SLFCU does not, and will not, sell any member information to list services, telemarketers, or companies not associated with SLFCU.** SLFCU does not share information collected on former members except as permitted or required by law.  

We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who have a  
  
specific business purpose in utilizing your data. Our employees are trained in the importance of  
  
maintaining confidentiality and member privacy. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to safeguard your non-public personal information.  

 **Information We Collect and May Disclose About You**  

We collect the following non-public personal information about you from a variety of sources:  
  
·         Information we receive from you on membership and loan applications and other forms such as your name, address, social security number, assets and income;  
  
·         Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others such as your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions and credit card usage;  
  
·         Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency such as your credit worthiness and credit history;  
  
·         Information obtained when verifying the information you provide on applications or other forms, such as your employment history with current or former employers and account balances with other institutions where you conduct financial transactions.  

We may disclose some or all of the information we collect to vendors that work for the Credit Union, other financial institutions that perform services or joint marketing on our behalf such as CUNA Mutual Group, or our affiliates such as Consumer Financial Services LLC. We structure all of these relationships to protect your information.  

We may disclose information we collect about you to non-affiliated third parties (such as our credit card processor or account statement-printing vendor) as permitted or required by law. These disclosures typically include information to process transactions on your behalf, conduct the operations of the Credit Union, and follow your instructions as you authorize, or protect the security of Credit Union financial information.  

If you have any questions or concerns about Sandia Laboratory Federal Credit Union’s Privacy Notice, please contact us in Albuquerque at 505/293-0500, toll free at 800/947-5328, or e-mail  
  
ebranch@slfcu.org.  

|  |  |   
  
---  
|  |
